Guide to the Murray Webb Latimer papers, 1930-1980 MS2082
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Murray Webb Latimer papers
1930-1980
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Latimer, Murray Webb
MS2082
69.5 Linear Feet
Collection contains correspondence, actuarial reports, census data, legislative documents, budgets, reports, articles, speeches, bulletins, and drafts from 1930 to 1980. Topics within this collection includes pensions, labor unions, wages, insurance companies in America and Canada, legislation related to health issues and social security. Some of the companies and organizations with data in this collection are the Kaiser Frazer Corporation, Kaiser Motor Corporation, Sandia Corporation, Civil Service Employees Association, AT&T, Washington Post, and National Council of Senior Citizens.
Box 139
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Historical or Biographical Note
Murray Webb Latimer (1901-1985) was a pension expert who helped draft the original Social Security Act and later headed his own industrial relations firm. He is considered one of the founding fathers of the Social Security System.
Latimer was born in Clinton, Mississippi. In 1919, Latimer received a B.A. from Mississippi College and in 1924 an M.B.A. from Harvard. From 1926-33, he was employed as a pension specialist for Industrial Relations Counsellors, Inc in New York. His career with the Federal Government began in 1933. From 1934-46 he served as chairman of the Railroad Retirement Board, the agency which administered the pension, death, unemployment, and sick benefits for the railroads in the United States. In 1943, he was assigned to the State Department as chief executive officer of its emergency office of Foreign Relief and Rehabilitation Operations. He also was a member of the U.S. delegation to the United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration.
His work with the Social Security System came in 1934-35 when he was chair of a special committee of President Franklin D. Roosevelt's Committee on Economic Security. He left the government in 1947 after completing a guaranteed annual wage study originally order by President Roosevelt. He opened his own industrial relations consulting firm, where he designed and drafted pension plans for such clients as the United Steelworkers of American and AT&T. He retired in 1983.
Latimer was a member of the American Academy of Actuaries and a fellow of the Conference of Actuaries in Public Practice.
Murray Webb Latimer died in 1985 at the age of 84.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, actuarial reports, census data, legislative documents, budgets, reports, articles, speeches, bulletins, and drafts. The material covers the years 1930-80. Topics within this collection includes pensions, labor unions, wages, insurance companies in America and Canada, legislation related to health issues and social security. Some of the companies and organizations with data in this collection are the Kaiser Frazer Corporation, Kaiser Motor Corporation, Sandia Corporation, Civil Service Employees Association, AT&T, Washington Post, and National Council of Senior Citizens.
Collection Organization
Organized into six series: Papers, Atomic Energy Commission, Railroad Retirement Board, Publications, Tabular studies, and Railroad companies.
Collection note
Please note: series 5 and 6 are not processed.
Related Materials
MS2135 Box 40 Folder 10 contains a recording of Latimer
Railroad companies; Unemployment insurance; Insurance; Retirement; Railroads; Pensions; Social security; U.S. Atomic Energy Commission; United States. Railroad Retirement Board; National Council of Senior Citizens; Sandia Corporation; United Steelworkers of America; Western Conference of Teamsters; American Telephone and Telegraph Company; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company; American Psychiatric Association; Latimer, Murray Webb; Industrial Relations Counselors, inc.; Kaiser Motors Corporation
- Papers, 1930-1980; MS2082 Series 1; 39.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains correspondence, speeches, articles, manuscript, lists of Actuaries, amendments, legislation, reports, statistics, valuation data, and pension plans. The material dates from 1930-80. This material appears to relate to both Latimer's personal life and his career as a government economist dealing with pension, retirement, and insurance issues for many groups in the United States. These groups are both corporations and labor groups including among others the American Federation of Hosiery Workers, railroad brotherhoods, Communications Workers of America, Philadelphia Orchestra Association, and United Steel Workers.
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-,A-Z, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Original numbering system: L 1.1
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-,A-M, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L1.2
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-N-Z, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-Z, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L1.31
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-M, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L1.4.01
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-N-Z, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L1.4.02
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-Z, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L1.5.01.02
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-M, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L1.6.1
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-N-Z, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L1.6.2
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-Z, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L1.7.1.2
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-Z, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L1.8.1.2
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence- H.L Brunson file, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L1.8.1
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-Z, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L1.9.1.2
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-M, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L1.10
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-N-Z, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-M, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system: L1.11
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-N-Z, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Papers, undated (Box 2)
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-Z, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L1.12
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-A-M, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L1.13
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence-N-Z, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1947 January-1947 June (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L1.14
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1947 July-1947 November (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L1.15
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1947 December (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1948 January-1948 June (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L1.16
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1948 July-1948 December (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L1.17
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1949 January (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L1.18
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1949 February-1949 June (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1949 July-1949 September (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L1.19
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1949 October-1949 December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1950 January-1950 June (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L1.20
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1950 July-1950 December (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L1.21
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1951 January-1951 June (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: L1.22
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1951 July-1951 December (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system: L1.23
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1952 January-1952 June (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system: L1.24
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1952 July-1952 December (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system: L1.25
  - Papers, undated (Box 3)
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1953 January-1953 June (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L1.26
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1953 July-1953 December (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L1.27
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1954 January-1954 June (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L1.28
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1954 July-1954 December (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L1.29
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1955 January-1955 June (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L1.30
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1955 July-1955 December (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1956 January-1956 June (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L1.32
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1956 July-1956 December (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L1.33
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L1.34
  - Personal Papers-Correspondence, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L1.35
  - Personal Correspondence, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L1.36
  - Personal Correspondence, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L1.37
  - Personal Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L1.38
  - Personal COrrespondence, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: L1.39
  - Personal Correspondence L. M. SOLOMAN, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system: L1 40
  - Personal Correspondence L. M. SOLOMAN, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system: L1.41
  - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system: L1.42
  - Papers, undated (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L1.43
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L1.44
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L1.45
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L1.46
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L1.47
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L1.48
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L1.49
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L1.50
  - M..W.L., Miscellaneous insurance papers, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L2
  - Personal Correspondence, 1948 August (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L2.a
  - Personal Papers, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L2.b
  - Personal-1536 U Street, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L2.c
  - Correspondence--Estate, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L2.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 5)
  - Personal- Publicity-Biograpical Statements- Photographs, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L2.2
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L2.3
  - M.W.L., Prudential Insurance of America coverage, correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L2.4
  - Acts, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L3
  - Loyalty Cases, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L4
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY-Membership List ( of those sent final report), undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L5
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY-Reports and Studies (General), undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L5.a
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY- Publications and Periodicals Catalogs and Bibliographies, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L5.b
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY- Publications,Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L5.c
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY- Public Relatons- Speeches by M.W.L, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L5.d
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY-Public Relatos, Newspaper and Magazine Clippings, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L5.e
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY-Public Relations, Press Releases, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L5.f
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY- Treasury Department, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L5.g
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY- Statistics Division, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L5.h
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY- Stabilization Studies Division (Memos from I. Kaplan), undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: L5.i
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY- Presonnel, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system: L5.j
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY- Newspaper Clippings, 1946 June-1946 August (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system: L5.k
  - OFFICE OF WAR MOBILIZATION AND RECONVERSION, GUARANTEED WAGE STUDY-Legislation, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system: L5.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 6)
  - NATIONAL BLUE CROSS: -National Blue Cross, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L7
  - NATIONAL BLUE CROSS: -Hearing on proposed rate increase, by Hospital Service of Philadelphia, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L7.1
  - NATIONAL BLUE CROSS: -Hospital Service Association Service of Pennsylvania, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L7.la
  - NATIONAL BLUE CROSS: -New York, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L7.2
  - NATIONAL BLUE CROSS: -New Jersey, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L7.4
  - NATIONAL BLUE CROSS: -Misc. Pamphlets, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L7.5
  - NATIONAL BLUE CROSS: -Kentucky, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L7.6
  - Papers, undated (Box 7)
  - Internal Revenue Code-Regulations, social [?security?] Insurance, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L8
  - Conference of Actuaries in Public Practice, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L9.1
  - Impact of Pension Funds on the National Economy" - Remarks of G. W. Mitchell, Member of Board of Governors of Federal Reserve System, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L9.3
  - National Conference on Special Services New Orleans,La, 1970 December 13-16 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L9.4
  - Conferences,American Management Association, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L9.9
  - Applications Forms, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L10
  - Union Health, Welfare, and Pension Funds, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L11
  - American Pension Conference, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L12
  - LABOR DEPARTMENT: -Committee on Labor Costs in Relation to Older Workers, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L13
  - LABOR DEPARTMENT: -Relation of Pension Costs to the Employment of Older Persons, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L13.1
  - LABOR DEPARTMENT: -Work-sheets(calculations) for 1965 Study of Employee Hiring Ages (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system :L13.2
  - Papers, undated (Box 8)
  - Labor Health Conference, 1858 June (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L14
  - Dental care, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L15
  - M.W.L Railroad Pension Review, 1931-1934 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L20. 1
  - M.W.L Railroad Pension Review, 1935-1937 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L20.2
  - Licensing(Latimer and Staff), undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L30
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L30.1
  - Old-Age,Surviver, Disability Health Insurance- Statitical Data, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L40.1
  - M.W.L, Congressional Retirement Study, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L43
  - M.W.L.,Personal-Civil Service Retirement Study, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L44
  - Civil Service Retirementand Disability Fund-Annual Reports, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L44.1
  - CIVIL SERVICE COMMISSION: -Retirement Reports, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L44.3
  - CIVIL SERVICE COMMISSION: -Group Life Insurance and Health Benefit Reports, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L44.4
  - CIVIL SERVICE COMMISSION: - Civil Service Retirement Act, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L44.5
  - M.W.L Persnal- Articles and Speeches, 1934-1942 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L45.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 9)
  - SPEECHES AND ARTICLES, 1943-1946 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L45.2
  - SPEECHES AND ARTICLES, 1947 January-May (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L45.3
  - SPEECHES AND ARTICLES, 1947 June-December (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L45.5
  - SPEECHES AND ARTICLES, 1948 January-1952 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - National Health Survey,(Labor Advisory Committee on Statistics), 1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L46
  - Senate Committee on Aging, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L47
  - Private Pension Plan Survey, Senate Labor Sub-committee, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L47.a2
  - M.W.L. Personal, Wharton School of Finance and Commerce Economics 428- Social. Insurance, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L48
  - National Treasury Employees Union, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L48.1
  - Tax Sheltered Annuities( for public schools systems), undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L49
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.:-Correspondence, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L50.la
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC., 1935 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L50.lb
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC., 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L50.1c
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.:-Interborough Rapid Transit Company, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L50.2
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.:- The Texas Company, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: L50.3
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.:-Bryce M. stewart Material, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system: L50.4
  - Papers, undated (Box 10)
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.: memoranda to clients #5- #40, 1935-1938 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L50.6a
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.: memoranda to clients,, ,# 41, 1939-1957 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L50.6b
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.: Memos 461-72, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L50.6c
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.: Memos 4473-#94, 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L50.6D
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.: Memos, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L50.6E
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.: Memos, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L50.6F
  - INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS COUNSELERS INC.: Publications, National Assoc. of Manufacturers-Memos, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L50.7
  - Inter-American Association of Social Security Actuaries, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L51
  - Major Medical Expence, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L52
  - MISSISSIPPI COLLEGE SPEECH, DEDICATION: -Correspondence, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L54
  - MISSISSIPPI COLLEGE SPEECH, DEDICATION: -Unfinished Manuscript, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L54.1
  - MISSISSIPPI COLLEGE SPEECH, DEDICATION: -Unused Manuscript- Tables, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L54.1a
  - Papers, undated (Box 11)
  - MISSISSIPPI COLLEGE SPEECH, DEDICATION: -Background Material, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L54.1b
  - MISSISSIPPI COLLEGE SPEECH, DEDICATION: -Background Tables, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L54.1c
  - MISSISSIPPI COLLEGE SPEECH, DEDICATION: -Manuscript, 1964 May 30 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L54.1d
  - Aging, Miscellaneous Material, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L55
  - Age discrimination in Employment, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L55.1
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L55.A
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: -Insurance Company Proposals, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L55.A1
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: -Insurance Program Bids and Contracts, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L55.A2
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: -Trust Agreements, Pension Plans, Contract Employees, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L55.A3
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: -Pamphlets, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L55.A3a
  - Papers, undated (Box 12)
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: -Valuations and Memos,Prior, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L55.B1
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: -Contract Employees Memos, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L55.B2
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: - Health And Insurance Memos and Costs, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L55.B3
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: - Valuation, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L55.B5
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: -Staff Plan, 1975 December 31-1976 December 31 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L55.B6
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: -Staff Plans, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L55.B6A
  - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF SENIOR CITIZENS: -Trust Agreements, Staff Pension Plans,Regular Employment, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L55.B6B
  - American Academy of Actuaries, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L56
  - International Actuarial Assn.and its Bulletin, ASTIN, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L56.1
  - Casulty Actuarial Society, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L56.2
  - Service Tables, Rates and Salrey Scales, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L57.1
  - Service Table Commutation Columns, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)